Guide to the Frank Pagliaro Construction Records Collection 1914-1971 PR 282
New-York Historical Society
- Series XI: Louis (Luigi) Gerbino Personal Effects
  - Louis Gerbino & Frank Pagliaro: Personal Finances, 1920-1939 (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Louis Gerbino & Frank Pagliaro: Personal Finances, 1920-1939 (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Louis Gerbino AKA "Equario Pagliaro" (d.) & Manhattan Art Stone (p.): Law Suit, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Louis Gerbino/Anna Gerbino & Ignazio Palgiaro: Personal Effects, - 1938 (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Louis Gerbino Personal Finances: Checks, Dividends, General Business Documents, 1918-1939 (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Louis Gerbino: Properties Offered for Purchase Document, 1921-1929 (Box 13, Folder 118)
- Series XII: Cornell University Exam Books
  - Cornell University Exams, 1921-1922 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - College of Civil Engineering Exams, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - College of Civil Engineering Exams, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - College of Civil Engineering Exams, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - College of Civil Engineering Exams, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Cornell University Exams, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Cornell University College of Engineering Exams, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Cornell University College of Engineering Exams, Unknown (Box 15, Folder 126)
- Series XIII: Architect Publications
  - Architecture and Design Magazine, Issues Featuring The Work of George Wellington Stoddard A.I.A., Bertram A. Weber A.I.A., H.R.H. Construction Corp., & John L. Volk - Oversized, 1939-1948 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - Architecture Monographs Featuring the Work of Jerome Robert Cerny, Bradley Delehanty, James W. O'Connor, & George Fred Pelham, Jr. - Oversized, 1937-1939 (Box 16, Folder 142)
  - Executive Health, Vol. III - Vol. VIII, with Missing Issues, Unknown (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Executive Health, Vol. IX - Vol. XI, with Missing Issues, Unknown (Box 15, Folder 128)